Guide to the Betsy Wade Papers WAG.020
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III. Newpaper Guild of New York, 1966-1984; 7.75 linear feet in 15 manuscript boxes and 1 half manuscript box
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- International Executive Board (IEB) -- Collective Bargaining Committee, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- International Executive Board (IEB) -- Committees, 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- International Executive Board (IEB) -- Constitution Committee, 1976-1979 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- International Executive Board (IEB) -- Contracts Committee, 1976-1981 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- International Executive Board (IEB) -- Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- International Executive Board (IEB) -- Elections, 1979-1981 (Box 14, Folder 14-15)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- International Executive Board (IEB) -- Finance and Administration Committee, 1976-1982 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- International Executive Board (IEB) -- Human Rights Committee, 1976-1981 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- International Executive Board (IEB) -- Minutes, 1975-1982 (Box 15, Folder 3-7)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- Pension Plans, January 1973 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- Pension Trust, 1978-1981 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- International Executive Board (IEB) -- Reports (Betsy Wade), 1975-1981 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- International Executive Board (IEB) -- Reports (Regional Vice Presidents), 1977-1982 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- International Executive Board (IEB) -- Special Defense Fund Committee, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- International Executive Board (IEB) -- Statements, Resolutions and Recommendations, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- Membership, 1979-1981 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- Officers List, 1977-1981 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- Organizing, 1975-1981 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- Organizing -- Anti Organizing Pamphlets, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- Special Merger Committee, 1979-1982 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- Strike Benefits -- Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- Strike Policies, 1976-1980 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- Unit Clarification, 1972-1979 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - News Women's Club of New York -- Awards, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Page One Awards, 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Providence Newspaper Guild -- "The Follies of '81" (program), 1981 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Rank and File Slates -- Guild Watch, 1993-1995 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Rank and File Slate Leaflets, 1992-1995 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Reuters Unit, 1978-1984 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Shadlen, Conrad (Private Bargaining Agent) -- Correspondence, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Standard and Poor Unit -- Sex Discrimination Complaints, 1977-1980 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Time Inc. Unit, 1980-1984 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Tri-Council (Great Lakes, Midwest, and Southern District Councils) -- Minutes, Agendas, Reports, Notices, 1979-1982 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - United Automobile Workers (UAW), District 65, 1978-1982 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Wade, Betsy -- Speeches, 1979-1983 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Wade, Betsy -- Notes, 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Waterbury American Republican Unit -- Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Western District Council, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Wire Service Guild, 1979-1982 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Responsibility Slate Cartoons, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 005, Folder 9)
- Series IV. New York Walking Tours, 1979-1993; .25 linear feet in 1 half manuscript box
  This series consists of research files documenting historical walking tours in New York City, the majority of which focus on labor history. Materials include flyers, pamphlets, calendars, schedules, photographs, newspaper clippings, correspondence, and a piece of International Ladies Garment Workers Union fabric.
  This series has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged in the order in which they were received from the donor.
  - New York City Labor History Walking Tours, 1979-1993 (Box 17, Folder 6-8)